

# **GILBERT JOSE**

WEB DEVELOPER

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript
React
Firebase
HTML5, CSS3
Responsive Design
Sass
JavaScript tooling with Gulp
Git and GitHub
Visual Studio Code
Website Accessibility

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Team player
Self-motivated
Courteous and conscientious
Organized
Time management
Driven to learn and grow

#### CONTACT

P: 416-275-8784 E: code@gilbertjose.ca W: www.gilbertjose.ca

#### SOCIAL



linkedin.com/in/gilbertjose



github.com/bet-code



@gilbert\_j5

### **ABOUT**

I am a web developer and technology enthusiast with over 10 years of professional IT technical support and customer service experience in a telecommunication environment. Looking forward to working in a team and grow within an organization.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

TECHXPERT TECHNICAL SUPPORT

Rogers Communication | Jun 2011 - Jul 2016

- Resolve complex technical issues such as PC optimization, virus eradication, data recovery, network connectivity etc.
- Provide support on wide range of Operating Systems such as iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows and Mac
- Setup and configure home networking devices, such as home routers, wireless printers, security cameras etc.
- Problem solve with emphasis on fixing root cause.

WIRELESS LIVE CHAT TECHNICAL SUPPORT Rogers Communication | Sep 2009 - Jun 2011

- Utilize vendor's software and tools to identify and support issues such as software incompatibility, data synchronization, backup and OS re-install.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot mobile network connectivity.
- Configure and troubleshoot mobile OS settings, email and device features.

#### **EDUCATION**

WEB DEVELPMENT IMMERSIVE CERTIFICATE

HackerYou College of Technology | Jan 2017- Dec 2017

COMPUTER SYSTEM AND NETWORKING Xintra College | 2002 - 2003